{
    "subject": "Abel_Gance",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Au_Secours!",
    "human_readable": "Abel Gance created Au Secours!",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8146286010742188,
            "question": "Who created the film Au Secours!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.516750156879425,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by Abel Gance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4934999644756317,
            "question": "What are some notable works by Abel Gance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46734118461608887,
            "question": "When was the film Au Secours! released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44788527488708496,
            "question": "Where was Au Secours! filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4327079951763153,
            "question": "Is Abel Gance a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3450464606285095,
            "question": "What is known about Abel Gance's filmmaking style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30206993222236633,
            "question": "What impact did Abel Gance have on cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27702829241752625,
            "question": "What genre is the film Au Secours!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15613281726837158,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Abel Gance."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Abel Gance created Au Secours!",
            "html": "yago_4152_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Au Secours!",
            "html": "yago_4152_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did Abel Gance have on cinema?",
            "html": "yago_4152_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Abel Gance's filmmaking style?",
            "html": "yago_4152_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4152_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4152_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4152_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4152_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4152_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4152_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4152_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4152_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4152_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4152_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of whether the triple \"Abel Gance created Au Secours!\" is supported by the documents:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that in several documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_4152/re-ranker-msmarco/65.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_4152/re-ranker-msmarco/83.txt), it is mentioned that Abel Gance directed the film \"Au Secours!\" (1924) and made it as a result of a bet with Max Linder. This information directly supports the triple statement, indicating that the answer is indeed \"yes\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Abel Gance created Au Secours!\". For instance, multiple sources mention that \"Au secours!\" is a film directed by Abel Gance, and details about its creation are provided, such as it being made in response to a bet between Abel Gance and Max Linder."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}